{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932731591","data":{"timestamp":" 946932731590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASI"," userResponse":" NASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932734853","data":{"timestamp":" 946932734853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932737843","data":{"timestamp":" 946932737842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZI"," userResponse":" NAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932740908","data":{"timestamp":" 946932740908"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naye"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932744209","data":{"timestamp":" 946932744208"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nazo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAZO"," userResponse":" NAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932747245","data":{"timestamp":" 946932747245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nane"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANE"," userResponse":" NANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932749841","data":{"timestamp":" 946932749840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYO"," userResponse":" NAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932752956","data":{"timestamp":" 946932752955"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWE"," userResponse":" NAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932755960","data":{"timestamp":" 946932755960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nami"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932759055","data":{"timestamp":" 946932759054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NARO"," userResponse":" NARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.na.rand.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932762527","data":{"timestamp":" 946932762525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932762660","data":{"timestamp":" 946932762660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" c77da2ed-78a4-4a3c-8854-434ead820c56"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.na.rand.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" naro"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NARO"," userResponse":" NARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932784909","data":{"timestamp":" 946932784909"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naro_goti-miti-naro"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naro"," userResponse":" naro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932795406","data":{"timestamp":" 946932795406"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_kisu-nasi-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932808114","data":{"timestamp":" 946932808114"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nazo_tatu-nazo-gogo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nazo"," userResponse":" nazo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932818621","data":{"timestamp":" 946932818621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-nono-hizi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932827666","data":{"timestamp":" 946932827666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-zake-mpya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932836390","data":{"timestamp":" 946932836389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_naro_naro-wenu-haja"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" naro"," userResponse":" naro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932845452","data":{"timestamp":" 946932845452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nalo_ziwe-hiyo-nalo"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nalo"," userResponse":" nalo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932853938","data":{"timestamp":" 946932853938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_nasi-bado-zuri"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932862883","data":{"timestamp":" 946932862883"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nanu_soko-kuwa-nanu"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nanu"," userResponse":" nanu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932871827","data":{"timestamp":" 946932871827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_dawa-nasi-wali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nasi"," userResponse":" nasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.na.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932877608","data":{"timestamp":" 946932877606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 5b236b40-4dbe-4de5-a224-e3ce666e30ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.na.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nasi_dawa-nasi-wali"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932907310","data":{"timestamp":" 946932907310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nangila_najiuliza_nangila_nayo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932913954","data":{"timestamp":" 946932913954"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_nahitaji_naweza_nasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932921558","data":{"timestamp":" 946932921558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_nahitaji_naweza_nasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932932243","data":{"timestamp":" 946932932243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_nahitaji_naweza_nasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932938886","data":{"timestamp":" 946932938886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" najiuliza_najiuliza_nafuu_nasi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932946450","data":{"timestamp":" 946932946450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" najiuliza_najiuliza_nafuu_nasi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932953084","data":{"timestamp":" 946932953084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_namukhaywa_nani_nasi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932959723","data":{"timestamp":" 946932959723"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_najua_naro_nambuya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932966341","data":{"timestamp":" 946932966340"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" namna_najua_namna_nahitaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932972962","data":{"timestamp":" 946932972962"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_nasi_nafuu_nafasi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932979609","data":{"timestamp":" 946932979609"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nami_nanu_nami_namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932986269","data":{"timestamp":" 946932986269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nafasi_nayo_nafasi_namna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946932993727","data":{"timestamp":" 946932993727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nafasi_nayo_nafasi_namna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933001620","data":{"timestamp":" 946933001619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 815814d5-618d-4907-9850-3f0da7914683"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nafasi_nayo_nafasi_namna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933031035","data":{"timestamp":" 946933031035"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nangila_najiuliza_nangila_nayo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933037722","data":{"timestamp":" 946933037721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_nahitaji_naweza_nasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933044351","data":{"timestamp":" 946933044351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" najiuliza_najiuliza_nafuu_nasi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933050984","data":{"timestamp":" 946933050983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_namukhaywa_nani_nasi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933057611","data":{"timestamp":" 946933057611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_najua_naro_nambuya"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933064235","data":{"timestamp":" 946933064235"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" namna_najua_namna_nahitaji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933070865","data":{"timestamp":" 946933070865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nasi_nasi_nafuu_nafasi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933077512","data":{"timestamp":" 946933077511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nami_nanu_nami_namukhaywa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933084155","data":{"timestamp":" 946933084155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nafasi_nayo_nafasi_namna"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933090816","data":{"timestamp":" 946933090813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" nawe_nafuu_nawe_nalo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.na.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946933102864","data":{"timestamp":" 946933102863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_235149"," gameId":" 872822e0-0f84-4135-9c35-33f6d02846fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.na.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nawe_nafuu_nawe_nalo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}